I'm Nishimura, the prosecutor.
You have the right to remain silent
if you don't wish to speak.
You were arrested for the crime
of arson of inhabited buildings.
Please confirm. First, your name…
Place of birth, Yokohama.
Currently unemployed.
Do you affirm these facts
I've read as being true?
Is this all correct?
I first wanted to become a prosecutor
during the fall of ninth grade.
-I was 15 years old.
-I'm going now.
That morning,
I left the house to go to school.
But when I came to a traffic light,
my body froze all of a sudden.
Shaking, premonition, a sense of panic…
Kana Kana, come here.
CRIMES OF CORRUPTION!
FABRICATED BY THE PROSECUTOR
I rushed back home, and what I saw was…
I wanted to know the truth.
That was the sole reason
I wanted to become a prosecutor.
What is this?
My aspiration has become a reality.
Now, I'm opening the door
to find out if this love is real.
Could I indict the one I love?
And could you judge this love?
SHINANO UNIVERSITY
I met him for the first time in the summer
during my sophomore year at university.
Show me.
W-What?
Please.
-Huh?
-Show me.
-What?
-Your answers, so, I, can, cheat.
I can't flunk this.
N-No. Impossible.
I really need to do this. Come on.
Please! Please!
Just this once, that's it.
No, really.
Please.
That was the first crime
I ever committed.
I'm serious. You have beautiful hair!
Hey.
Hey, wait.
-Wait.
-Don't follow me.
Look what I got.
You dropped this.
Thanks for the other day.
Because of you…
Ta-da.
REPORT CARD GRADES
PASS, FAIL, PASS, PASS…
That's nice.
Law major?
-Yes.
-Me too.
-Don't you know me?
-No.
-Haven't you seen me around?
-Hey. Stop that, Masaki.
-You're rarely here, calm down.
-Here.
-Thank you.
-You're Kanade Nishimura, right?
-Yes.
I'm Tomomi Mori, I think we're both taking
Social Security Law Studies.
I think so.
My name is Kaori.
Hey, have some manners.
I did kind of know those two.
Law students are mostly male
so they stood out.
And this guy is Masaki.
He's probably in the same class as you.
What? Today's only the third time
you came to school this year?
I do come to school.
I just don't attend lectures.
It's just the third time
you've attended a lecture, right?
That's right.
Why?
I'm not interested.
But you don't want to fail?
I don't care if I do or not.
What? Then why did you…
cheat on the test?
Because…
isn't it thrilling?
Don't expect
a normal conversation with him.
He's kind of a scumbag.
There's something wrong with him
as a person.
Am I that bad though?
-Isn't he?
-He is.
But there aren't many scumbags
out there today, so it's refreshing.
True.
Thank you very much for harshly
complimenting me. Thank you.
-Give me.
-Aww.
Hey, don't.
Tastes terrible.
-Who cares what you think? I like it.
-How can you drink so much of that crap?
Tomo, Kaori, and Masaki were all
the kind of people I had never met before.
Hey, stop it!
Is she his girlfriend?
No.
Probably not.
Hey, you want a drink too, Kana Kana?
Wait. Why are you calling me Kana Kana?
Huh? Well, because of that.
How long have you been using that?
Since kindergarten?
Umm…
Hey, I've got a hunch.
-What?!
-Yoink!
See?
Mm-hmm.
-Cute.
-You look good.
Hey. Jeez.
There you are.
-I wasn't sure.
-You're late.
Who's this?
Kanade. Isn't she cute?
Yeah. Cute!
In high school, I had made myself
invisible after my father's incident.
I had nothing to lean on
except for studying.
Being a serious student
was my only strong point.
Introduce yourself!
But then I made friends.
-I remember that!
-Seriously?
Kaori, Tomo,
Masaki, Yuki,
and me.
We were always together.
It was the first time
I was enjoying my youth.
The meat is done. Here you go.
Come on everyone!
You burnt all of them!
I have one more left!
There are only vegetables left.
I felt like I could finally
breathe in deeply.
Hey!
-Ahh!
-Don't do that!
I didn't think the day would come
when I could laugh from my heart.
Take that! And that!
Amazing.
It's so beautiful.
As if it were a painting.
It is…
Guess what?
I'm glad I chose this university.
Let's be friends forever.
Hmm?
Huh? Who just said something
so unbelievably cliché?
You must have misheard. Or hallucinated.
I was serious!
I really thought so, so I said it.
Yeah, don't make fun of her.
Don't mock our… friendship!
You're ruining the sunset!
You're ruining our friendship!
"You ruined it!"
Hey.
You know what? My father…
-Huh?
-Your father?
What?
My father…
used to call me Kana Kana
when I was small.
That's why my mother embroidered the name
Kana Kana on my handkerchief.
My father…
died when I was in ninth grade.
I'm sorry.
We were living in Tokyo then.
He left my mother and me
and took his own life.
Suicide?
There was a lot going on at work...
Yes. Yes, I understand.
Am I the only one summoned?
He was a public prosecutor in Tokyo.
Prosecutor.
Yes.
Is that why you're a law major?
I wanted to take the bar exam.
After my dad's suicide,
my mom and I moved to Nagano
where my mom is from.
But eventually,
rumors about my dad quickly spread.
I couldn't make any friends.
So I was always studying.
Even after entering university,
it was hard to open up to other students.
I thought for sure the next four years
would be lonely again.
That's why…
I'm so happy right now,
because you all are with me.
Sorry to burden you
with heavy stuff like this.
But I'm glad I told you.
It's my first time
to tell anybody about this.
Let's always be friends.
Forever.
For sure.
Kanade.
Hey.
All right.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Look.
My gratitude was genuinely from the heart.
And yet, the one
who first betrayed us was…
TWO YEARS LATER
IT'S RAINING HEAVILY, I CAN'T GO OUT.
IT'S CANCELED FOR SURE.
What are they saying?
Yuki doesn't want to go out in the rain.
Tomo's in the library.
She says the fireworks--
-That scared me!
-It's going to be okay.
I heard lightning doesn't strike cars.
Really?
Huh?
The windshield wipers stopped. Look.
It seems so.
Whoa! It's like a water slide.
I can't see anything in front of me.
Are we okay?
-If we die, we die together.
-No way!
I don't want to.
I really don't want to die.
You don't? I do.
I don't mind dying if it were with you.
What?
Please stop the car.
-It's fine!
-Just pull over somewhere.
The Shinshu fireworks are canceled,
as we thought.
Kaori and Yuki said they couldn't make it.
Oh yeah?
What are we going to do?
Want to stay here for a while?
Huh? Why?
Instead of fireworks…
Hmm? What?
I've never seen…
such a beautiful starry sky.
First time for me too.
"Such a beautiful starry sky."
Hey.
Then, how did you know about this place?
Why?
Just by chance.
Liar.
You even turned off the headlights--
Kanade.
I love you.
Hey, let me see your hand.
Hmm?
Do you know there's a way to hold hands
that can never be separated?
Use handcuffs?
-Not like that.
-Huh?
Just like an aspiring prosecutor.
What?
Hold your hand like this, L-shaped.
Then I do this.
Like that.
Try to get loose.
Hmm?
See?
I was hyperactive as a kid.
Aren't you still?
Now? I guess I still am.
My mom would always
hold my hand like this.
Oh. I see.
But…
she's gone away.
One day,
she disappeared.
Kanade.
I love you.
I'm never letting you go.
I feel the same.
When someone who you thought loved you
suddenly disappears,
it hurts. I know.
What?
I encouraged you so many times,
but you never wanted to.
Huh?
Contact lenses. You switched from glasses.
Yeah. I thought I should give them a try.
Uh-huh.
You look kind of pretty, Kanade.
You're glowing.
What?
Hey.
Do you want to go to karaoke?
I got some free tickets.
Karaoke?
I can't. I have to get to Civil Law class.
Come on.
Kaori!
Don't be a sourpuss like that.
-Show me your face. There!
-I'm not.
Stop it.
-Ow!
-You did it first!
But you're the one who started it!
Man, you have a short fuse!
Kaori said she wasn't accepted at Nanai.
What? But she said she was definitely
going to get the job…
She didn't pass the final interview.
She might be a bit unstable now
since her job-hunting isn't going well.
I see.
You know, Kaori often says
that she never can get
what she wants the most.
Her family's rich, so everything she has
is super expensive
like her car, clothes, and bags.
I don't know what her problem is.
But I guess it's part of her charm
that she openly expresses her feelings.
You're right.
I was aware that
Kaori had feelings for Masaki.
But…
I pretended not to notice
even though I did.
I'M STAYING OVER AT TOMO'S HOUSE
TONIGHT TO STUDY.
You liar!
Yeah, I lied. So what?
Whom do you think I lied for?
You don't have to lie.
I can go to your house and say,
"I'm her boyfriend. I often ask her
to stay overnight at my house."
-You would, huh?
-I can do that.
"Boyfriend"? You can say that?
Can't I say that?
Of course, you can.
Careful!
Because
it was my first love…
I didn't want to give Masaki away
to anybody else.
Sorry. Did I wake you?
I was already awake.
No!
What do you mean, "no"?
What a foolish and arrogant
love.
Huh? Where's Kaori?
Career Support Office.
She's getting nervous
about not having secured a job yet.
Really?
Oh, Kaori.
Hi. Long time no see.
-Hey.
-What do you want?
Aren't you going to the library?
Tomo and Masaki are there.
I don't need to.
I knew she was in a bad mood
not just due to failing with job-hunting.
It was also because of me and Masaki.
But I desperately denied it in my mind.
And the entrance exam for law school
was fast approaching.
I decided to apply
to the Metropolitan Law School after all.
Oh, really?
What are you going to do?
It's not possible for me to consider
a private school, so only public.
-Kaori's in a super crabby mood.
-I thought so.
How can she take it out on me like that?
Because it's you.
-Yeah.
-What? Me?
That's mean.
Hey, let's study, you guys.
We need to write a graduation thesis.
We don't have time.
Jeez.
Kaori still hasn't been
accepted for a job.
I heard.
-You knew?
-Yeah. She called me.
Oh, wait. Let's add this.
Thanks for the meal.
-Listen.
-Hmm?
I'm thinking of applying
to a law school in Tokyo.
I see. Are you still trying
to become a prosecutor?
Uh-huh.
It's just amazing to me
how you and Tomo can do that.
After two more years of studying,
you'll be taking the bar exam, right?
That's dedication.
Amazing.
What are you going to do
after graduation, Masaki?
I haven't thought about it yet.
I mean,
well, first of all,
I wonder if I can graduate.
I feel like…
what are we even doing?
What?
Half of Japan
is in a terrible state right now.
Whole towns gone, houses washed away.
So many people lost their family members.
But here we are leading normal lives.
Should we look for jobs
like nothing happened?
Well, maybe it's not for me to say.
Yeah, that's true.
It's not for you to say, Masaki.
Whoa. That hurt.
A future prosecutor for sure.
Don't make fun of me.
We really need to decide about our future.
Isn't it time to do that?
Do you mean that you want me
to follow the path set by society?
What if I followed it
but the path had potholes,
or the path was a rough one,
or it was the wrong one from the start?
Do I still keep running on it?
That's just…
a path to doom.
At that moment,
something reminded me of my father.
I thought of my father
who had been facing his doom on that day.
Don't do something like that.
That's going too far.
But you're the one who told me
how bad it would be if this were true.
-Yes, but--
-That's why I did research.
Why are you trying to stop me?
-But--
-You knew he was going out with her.
That's why you thought it was no good.
Kaori, hold on--
You thought he should know too.
I realize I shouldn't have
told you about it.
But even if it were true,
it's their problem and not ours.
We don't have the right to step in.
What good will it do, anyway?
You're being argumentative again.
I know that you like Masaki.
But that doesn't mean--
I don't have feelings for Masaki.
Not at all.
I'm just saying it because he's a friend.
Didn't I say, "Let's be friends forever"?
Who's the one that betrayed us?
Wasn't it Kanade?
Hey, stop.
I can't take all this
schoolgirl-level talk anymore.
Listen.
I have to finish my thesis,
and study to be able to enter law school.
I don't have time for trivial things
like love, so leave me out of it.
My life depends on my studies.
Hello?
Good morning.
Where are you going?
I got a call from a girl.
What?
Just kidding. To the store.
Then buy some ice cream.
Oh, maybe I'll go too--
No need to. Is vanilla okay?
Yeah, thanks.
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
I knew you would come.
Are you alone?
Yep.
Is there anyone in your room now?
No. What did you want to talk to me about?
Get in.
Just get in.
KAORI
YOU HAVE A NEW MESSAGE.
So, where are we going?
I shouldn't have come out
wearing only this.
It's cold…
Kaori, you're driving too fast--
Kanade was there, wasn't she?
She was there, right?
Jeez.
Interrogating me?
Whoa, that's dangerous.
You shouldn't be going out with Kanade.
Why?
Hey Kaori, say something. What is it?
Kanade's dad didn't commit suicide.
He was murdered.
What?
What the hell…
-What are you doing?!
-Like I said!
You shouldn't be seeing Kanade!
Why?!
Hey.
Do you want to die with me?
Huh?
Let's die together.
BYE
Kaori!
Why can't I ever get what I want the most?
Kaori, stop.
Come on, stop! This is nuts!
Why won't you believe me?!
Quit fooling around!
Because…
Kanade's dad was--
Don't say it!
Hello? Oh, Tomo. Is anything wrong?
Kanade? Where are you?
Tomo.
Kanade.
Why…
Why did Kaori…
Huh? Tomo?
MATSUMOTO HIGASHI POLICE STATION
Kaori had died in an accident,
said the police officer
in a business-like tone.
Did she die instantly?
Yes.
She must have lost control of the car
on a sharp curve on the way to Karuizawa.
The car was totaled.
We wanted to ask you
about Mr. Masaki Nogi who was with her.
Y-Yes.
Masaki lived.
At approximately what time
did Mr. Nogi leave the house?
Um, I think it was about 1 p.m.
Why did Mr. Nogi go out?
To go to the store.
That's what he told me.
Did he receive a call
on his cell phone at that time?
At 12:55 p.m.
-Um, officer.
-What is it?
This accident…
Do you suppose it was a crime?
Is that why you're…
This is just a formality.
This won't take long.
But after that, I was asked
the same questions repeatedly.
Were you waiting for me?
The police are questioning Masaki now.
And Kaori…
They're going to perform an autopsy.
I wonder if they suspect
it wasn't just an accident.
Hello.
Come with me.
This way, please.
-That man.
-Who?
It's Masaki's father.
Huh?
I'm the father of Masaki Nogi.
ATTORNEY KOICHIRO NOGI
I apologize for my son
causing so much trouble.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
Not at all.
I thought I needed to hear
all the details of this accident.
Have you talked to your son?
I went to the hospital,
but I wasn't allowed to see him
since he was still being questioned.
I apologize for the inconvenience
It's proper to investigate an accident.
But personally,
I would like to hear your view
of what happened.
Depending on what you say,
my son might need a lawyer.
That night, I went to Masaki's place
one more time.
But Masaki didn't come home.
I'M SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
MESSAGE ME WHEN YOU CAN.
He stopped contacting me after that night.
FUNERAL SERVICE FOR KAORI OIKAWA
In the end, the accident was blamed
on Kaori's negligence
and Masaki was not accused of any crime.
Everybody was crying,
but I couldn't cry.
I wanted to cry, but no tears came out.
I knew I had to mourn Kaori's death.
But all I could think of was Masaki,
who was not there.
Where are you going?
I got a call from a girl.
Just kidding.
I'll be right back.
And about what Masaki and Kaori
were doing on that day.
I really hated myself for it.
FUNERAL SERVICE FOR KAORI OIKAWA
Why didn't Masaki come?
This might be the end…
of our friendship.
After that,
we walked outside without saying a word.
Masaki.
Hey.
-Wait.
-Masaki.
Masaki.
Masaki!
Masaki, wait! Don't go! Masaki!
Stop! Wait!
Hey! Tell me what happened!
Was Kaori… Kaori…
Masaki!
I'm sorry!
I'm the one who…
What did
Masaki say at that moment?
Someone who I thought loved me
disappeared from in front of me again.
So once again
I had become all alone.
That year, I failed
my law school entrance exam.
I thought it was over for me.
12 YEARS LATER
YOKOHAMA DISTRICT
PUBLIC PROSECUTORS OFFICE CHUO BRANCH
YOKOHAMA, KANAGAWA PREFECTURE
KANADE NISHIMURA
TAKASHI OKUDA
12TH ANNIVERSARY BUDDHIST
MEMORIAL SERVICE FOR KAORI OIKAWA
A patient's condition worsened
so I'm working overnight again.
Thanks.
I understand. That's tough.
Won't this be the third night?
No, fourth.
Are you eating properly?
Tried all the box lunches sold
at the commissary.
The patient is male
in his twenties or thirties.
Identity is currently unknown.
He fell down the stairs at a subway
station during a scuffle.
Suffered a severe head blow.
Bleeding from the back of the head.
Chest and stomach also hit hard.
Consciousness is hazy.
Blood pressure 126 over 72. Heart rate 86.
SpO2 is 97%.
-Get ready to bring him in immediately.
-Yes.
YOKOHAMA MINATO GENERAL HOSPITAL
-Okay, bring him in.
-Okay.
I brought you this.
Thank you.
You brought me dinner too?
You said you tried all the box lunches.
Are you an angel?
You're exaggerating.
No, I'm serious. I'm so happy I could cry.
I'm glad.
Well, good luck with your work.
Thanks. Bye.
Oh, Kanade.
There's something I want to tell you
when things calm down.
Huh? What is it?
Not now. Let's talk
when there's more time.
I know you're busy. Thanks.
-No problem. Bye.
-Bye.
-Rear of head, side. Prepare for sutures.
-Yes.
You can't get up. Please don't move.
I must go somewhere…
You're still bleeding.
Don't get up.
-I'm fine.
-Please calm down.
Let's get you treated first.
Subtitle translation by: Ikuko Sachs
You're mine.
What really happened
between those two at that time?
You'd better not see Masaki.
I missed you.
Don't say you missed me.
This is a tough one.
An indictment is impossible.
Kaori was…
Why?